Hold on.
You should ask me first
before taking on a task.
What do you think?
Can we help?
What are these photos?
This suspect is cunning and seasoned,
his modus operandi
is extremely meticulous.
This is the only surveillance photo
that managed to capture his image.
What crime did he commit?
There have been frequent
homicides happening lately.
There were no obvious motives
for these murders,
and there were no specific connections
among the victims.
So we've deduced that
this is probably a serial homicide.
However, based on the clues
we have so far,
it seems that finding the killer
is not going to be that simple.
What?
What an inhuman pervert!
Who are you talking about?
It is imperative that
we help with this case!
We have to catch him as soon as possible
to prevent someone else
from becoming a victim!
Cheng Xiaoshi,
who gave you the right to speak for us?
Captain Xiao, don't listen to him.
It's still up to Lu Guang
to decide whether or not we can help.
I've looked at the general situation.
I'm sorry,
but this time,
there's nothing we can do.
Huh? Lu Guang, that's it?
Did you see it clearly?
Come on, let's go!
Hey, Lu Guang,
did you look at the photos carefully?
Shut up.
This is such a big case,
it's not a joke!
Anyway, I trust Lu Guang's judgment!
Lu Guang,
are you sure you saw it clearly?
You rarely ever say no.
Who was the one who
wanted to take a break?
Uh, I,
at the time,
I mean, but after that,
um, I just...
Come and receive guests!
Welcome, my landlady...
Boss, welcome in!
Hey, Xu Shanshan, why are you here
instead of studying?
Heh,
I'm here because I care about
the reemployment of the jobless.
Oh my,
so you're here to observe
the regular people's life.
It's no wonder,
after all, it's easy to grow out of touch
with society after studying so much,
I understand.
I have no choice,
unlike certain people,
who has rely on others
to survive even after graduation.
Mind your words,
who's relying on whom to survive?
Am I wrong?
The house is provided by Qiao,
the business is managed by Lu Guang,
aren't you just a good-for-nothing?
We are partners!
Don't poison the well if you don't
understand the situation clearly!
You only look at the surface of things,
you have such low EQ!
Quiet!
What have I always told you?
We must be considerate and
attentive to our customers.
What customers?
Unless...
Hmph, if it wasn't Qiao who convinced me
to come and give it a try,
I wouldn't even want to be here.
Shanshan,
what do you need help with?
Well,
let me tell you about it!
To begin,
let us return to
our vigorous
university days.
Do you still remember,
aside from the three of us,
there was another good friend
hanging around our beautiful Miss Xu?
Dong Yi.
Fine, then,
but you'll have to help me take this.
I'll come and get it from you at
your dormitory after I get back tonight.
What time?
If the entrance of
the dormitory is locked,
I'll have to throw it down to you
from the window.
The two of you are basically like
an old married couple,
why not clarify your relationship?
Pfft,
shouldn't boys take the initiative
in such matters?
Dong Yi,
over here!
Here, this is for you.
Two fried eggs, slightly spicy,
one sausage, no coriander.
Thanks, how much is it?
I'll transfer the money to you via WeChat.
Are you serious?
Talking about money hurts relationships.
Let's talk about
other conditions, shall we?
Uh...
Yes!
I've finally reached Platinum!
My ranking is King,
it's more than enough to carry you.
Is there something growing in my brain?
Why am I getting a headache
after just a few rounds?
What are you laughing at?
Hey, do you even have a conscience?
What if there's something
bad growing in my brain?
This problem is happening
to younger people nowadays.
Haven't you heard?
What?
You and Dong Yi were actually...
...a couple?
Who's the one with the low EQ?
Alas, it's been so many years,
yet the secret's still not out.
This is driving me crazy.
What?
Postgraduate?
Why are you so shocked?
I just want to further my studies,
which will give me a higher chance
of getting a better job in the future.
Beautiful Miss Xu,
for the next two years,
I won't be by your side,
so you'll have to
take good care of yourself.
Hey, hey, give me a break.
Who usually takes care of whom?
With you gone,
I can relax a lot more.
Oh wow, so you've always hated
having to put up with me.
But deep down in my heart I knew,
that she decided to stay behind
because of Dong Yi.
That tutor is awful!
All he cares about
is his business outside.
We hardly get to see him at all.
Stop complaining about it,
we have to rely on ourselves then.
The whole time,
she waited for the sentence
that never came.
Like an arrow, time flew by,
in the blink of an eye,
two years of postgraduate studies
passed in a flash.
Cheers!
We've graduated again!
Yeah, after bachelor's degree,
it's master's,
after master's, it's doctorate,
let's continue studying!
Oh no, I'm done with studying,
I have to look for a job.
Take care of yourselves!
--I'll drink to that!
--Xu Shanshan,
--All good things must come to an end.
--take a photo with Dong Yi!
Come here, why are you so shy?
Stop talking,
you're so old-fashioned.
Here, I only have
two photos from that night,
the other one is a selfie
I took for fun before dinner.
Cheng Xiaoshi, you're so annoying.
Why don't you tell us about
the specifics of the task first?
After that, I'll pick a suitable photo.
Let me tell you the rest of the story.
After the farewell dinner,
we went to a karaoke.
It ended pretty late,
and somehow,
I drank a little too much.
Oh?
And then...
Get lost,
it's not what you think it is!
I'm leaving.
--Bye-bye!
--See you guys next time.
Hope you all get rich in the future!
Hey, let's keep in touch.
Of course!
Goodbye, my fellow classmates!
--Hey, Dong Yi,
--Hey, Xu Shanshan.
--be careful.
--Let's keep in touch!
--Bye!
--Let's go, let's go.
--Sure!
--Keep in touch!
Don't go, no one is allowed to leave!
They're gone,
they're all already gone.
Then you should join me
for another round!
The signal is pretty weak here,
I can't get a ride,
I'll go over to that side and try.
All of them can leave,
except for you,
you're not allowed to go anywhere!
Xu Shanshan,
I have something to tell you.
Ugh!
At the time, I blacked out,
I didn't hear a single word he said.
After sobering up, I realised I had
done lots of embarrassing things,
and got myself in trouble,
I regret it so much!
If you care so much about what he said,
why didn't you just ask him
about it afterward?
It's because I care so much,
that's why I couldn't bring myself to ask.
I'm so afraid that the answer
is not going to be what I think it is.
Pfft, how dramatic.
Got it,
we can help you with this.
What?
You agree, just like that?
Hey wait a minute,
did you say help?
This is clearly a deal,
why should we do it for free?
She should at least give us
a little something in return.
Cheng Xiaoshi! You traitor!
I'm just trying to pay off your debt.
Hey, if you're willing to give
a discount, that's fine as well.
Not my face!
Hmph, it seems his brain
can't function properly
without a beating a day.
Hey Qiao,
how are they able to
get information of the past from photos?
Hmm, I don't know exactly.
They always do it alone every time,
it's very mysterious.
I can't really trust Cheng Xiaoshi.
I wonder if he'll do
anything questionable.
Is there no justice in this world?
How could you beat up the person
who's going to help you?
I... Hmm,
I... realized something.
Don't worry about it.
I think it's mainly Lu Guang's effort,
Cheng Xiaoshi is just a tool.
Lu Guang being reliable is good enough.
Cheng Xiaoshi,
what are you doing?
I just realized,
after entering the photo,
what I say, goes.
I can do whatever I want.
Xu Shanshan,
there are two internship positions
at my mom's hospital.
If we date,
she said that she could
arrange a position for you.
But, she doesn't really like
girls with long hair...
Huh?
What did you say?
Xu Shanshan,
you're going too far!
Even if you want to reject me,
you shouldn't ruin yourself like this!
Huh?
It was just a joke,
why is he having a breakdown?
That boy looked quite tough,
why is his heart so fragile?
Cheng Xiaoshi,
be careful with your current identity,
don't get Xu Shanshan in trouble.
Do you want me to reiterate
the three rules we agreed on?
No, don't start chanting
your cursed incantation.
Xu Shanshan.
Hmm?
It seems there's no one sitting here?
This feeling... is here again,
and her heart is beating
so much faster than before.
My chest feels so uncomfortable!
Pay attention
to where you put your hand.
No one,
you don't need to be so polite with me.
It's that temper of yours.
I'm afraid that if I don't ask you first,
you'd hit me till I run away.
Xu Shanshan,
take a photo with Dong Yi!
Come.
Come here.
Why are you so shy?
You lose! is here again,
Again! Again! Again!
Xu Shanshan,
it's been so many years, yet none of us
have heard you sing before,
why don't you sing a song today?
Pick any song,
I can sing anything!
Wow!
Hey, you're usually quite restrained,
but you're a little strange today.
This heartbeat is making me
so uncomfortable, I can't not drink.
Cheng Xiaoshi,
later you'll be drinking a bit too much.
After you come back, remember to go
downstairs and sleep on the couch.
Got it.
No wonder Xu Shanshan got drunk.
Hey, that's enough.
It doesn't seem like you have
anything to worry about,
I don't think you need to drink
to ease your sorrows, right?
You nerd, why are you always so rational?
Can't you follow your heart,
at least once?
Do you know why I chose
to further study back then?
No.
Because in our four years of university,
I've already gotten so used to it.
I've gotten used to having meals with you,
going to class with you,
playing games together,
taking walks aimlessly around the campus,
speaking thoughtless words
that we both understand.
So,
further studying had become
a means for me to escape,
but now,
I still have to choose
to leave eventually.
Leave?
It's because I care so much,
that's why I couldn't bring myself to ask.
I'm so afraid that the answer
is not going to be what I think it is.
Hey, Xu Shanshan,
the song we picked for you is here!
Here, take the mic.
That's amazing!
Hey, what's wrong with you guys?
Are you trying to trick me?
Hey, can you use your brain a little?
Why do you always start without
waiting for everyone to be ready?
I saw a good opportunity
to take down the enemy,
you guys are just slow!
Can you three look a little lively?
You look like three joss
sticks stuck in an urn,
where's the fun in that?
Hey, let me see if
you ruined my handsome face
with a blurry photo.
--Go away.
--Remember to come back often!
It wasn't easy to pass
the oral defense, stop cursing me.
Dong Yi,
from now on it's up to you
to take care of our beautiful Miss Xu.
Hey, don't you think
it's such a coincidence that
the both of us decided to further study?
Is it a coincidence?
I don't know,
there's so many of us who stayed
behind to further study after all.
You're no fun.
Tomorrow morning's class
is still at Yi Fu Building 201,
don't forget our usual.
I got it,
two fried eggs, slightly spicy,
one sausage, no coriander.
If it's possible,
I never want to say goodbye.
You sound so good.
You can really sing!
Xu Shanshan,
I can't believe that
after six years of friendship,
I never realized that
you could sing so well.
That was pretty good,
your breathing was quite stable.
Whenever he speaks,
her heart beats like crazy,
I think the only way is to...
Keep drinking!
My fellow brothers and sisters,
let's keep singing!
Bye-bye!
See you guys next time.
Hope you all get rich in the future!
Hey, let's keep in touch.
Of course!
Goodbye, my fellow classmates!
--Hey, Dong Yi,
--Hey, Xu Shanshan.
--be careful.
--Let's keep in touch!
--Bye!
--Sure!
Don't go, no one is allowed to leave!
They're gone,
they're all already gone.
Then you should join me
for another round!
The signal is pretty weak here,
I can't get a ride,
I'll go over to that side and try.
All of them can leave,
except for you,
you're not allowed to go anywhere!
So far so good.
Just a little more and we're finished.
Xu Shanshan,
I have something to tell you.
This person is so sneaky,
why does he look so familiar?
It's the serial killer from the photo!
Hey.
Cheng Xiaoshi!
I can't let him get away.
Xu Shanshan, are you sober now?
Damn it, my head is still dizzy.
Hey, why are you going there?
Cheng Xiaoshi,
have you lost your mind?
I just saw the suspect
from the surveillance photo.
Don't be foolish,
you can't catch him on your own.
Furthermore,
this guy is more trouble
than human traffickers.
But I can take a photo of his face,
at least it could serve as another clue
to help the police
resolve the case earlier.
Oh no, where's my phone?
Watch out, behind you!
Wait!
If you turn around suddenly,
you might trigger the suspect.
It might cause him to attack even quicker.
Then what am I supposed to do now?
Try to create a situation where
he wouldn't be able to attack,
then wait for an opportunity.
Can't attack, then...
Oh no,
I drank too much, I need to pee,
like a waterfall...
...streaming down...
Damn it, I forgot I'm a girl now...
Hurry and find another way!
Does he still intend to attack me
when I'm like this?
He truly is a pervert!
I'm just going to go for it!
Oh no, it's for real now!
The danger has been eliminated.
Where did he go?
No!
Take this!
It's me!
When did you learn self defense?
Dong Yi?
Where's the guy with the baseball cap?
Isn't this the mama's boy...
It's just a case of unrequited love
from a male classmate
who had the wrong intentions,
how did it get so exaggerated
and turned into a resolved urban mystery?
Does this bunch of unscrupulous media
have any bottom line?
Not only did they come up with
some baseless and exaggerated headline,
they even published her photo!
How's the task going?
I got distracted with catching a suspect.
I've written everything down.
Sure enough, Lu Guang is always reliable.
Oh right, I almost forgot
you had this ability.
So, what exactly did
Dong Yi say back then?
I've already passed
his message to Shanshan.
Xu Shanshan,
I have something to tell you.
When we were getting ready to graduate,
my parents had urged me to go back.
My dad has arranged everything for me,
so I've known all along
that after I graduate,
it's impossible for me
to stay in this city.
Dong Yi!
I never dared to confess my feelings...
What are you worrying about?
...because
I was afraid of hurting you, who had
stayed by my side for six years.
Oh, I'm just worrying
about the oral defense.
Hey, what's the big deal?
I'm meeting with Qiao Ling tonight
to watch a movie and relax,
do you want to come along?
That's all right,
I have some things to finish up.
Fine, then,
but you'll have to help me take this.
I'll come and get it from you at your
dormitory after I get back tonight.
What time?
If the entrance of
the dormitory is locked,
I'll have to throw it down to you
from the window.
The two of you are basically like
an old married couple,
why not clarify your relationship?
Now that I have to graduate,
I've finally realized,
no matter how hard the future may be,
I want to stay.
Because leaving you
hurts more than anything else.
Tomorrow morning at ten,
he has an important interview
at the Union Building,
and he hopes that you can accompany him.
It's obvious he's asking Shanshan
to make her feelings clear!
Let me ask her
if she went this morning.
Hehe,
so did you accompany him
to his interview this morning?
Wow, what a quick reply,
it seems everything went smoothly.
Hey, Dong Yi.
You're here to interview
for this company as well?
It's almost ten o'clock,
what are you doing standing around?
Oh, I'll go up in a moment.
Then I'll head up first.
Did the things I said that day
make her angry?
Hmm?
Shanshan, what is this?
Qiao Ling,
call Xu Shanshan and ask.
Ah, okay.
Xu Shanshan,
were you the one who sent
that message in the group?
I will...
...show up as promised.